export default data = [
  {
      question: "We have had plenty of rain so far this year, so there should be an ____ supply of fresh water this summer.",
      options: ["intense","ultimate","abundant","epidemic"],
      correct_option: "abundant"
  },
  {
      question: "I don’t know for sure what I am going to do this weekend, but ____ I plan to visit an old friend of mine in southern Taiwan.",
      options: ["tentatively","inevitably","unknowingly","numerously"],
      correct_option: "tentatively"
  },
  {
      question: "Our chemistry teacher was on a one-month sick leave, so the principal had to find a teacher to ____ for her.",
      options: ["recover","navigate","rehearse","substitute"],
      correct_option: "substitute"
  },
  {
      question: "The gym is closed on Monday for routine ____ work. The facilities are kept in good condition by the regular checking and repairing.",
      options: ["disturbance","eloquence","maintenance","alliance"],
      correct_option: "maintenance"
  },
  {
      question: "If you exercise regularly, your blood _____ will be improved, and you will feel more energetic.",
      options: ["fatigue","tranquility","fragrance","circulation"],
      correct_option: "circulation"
  },
  {
      question: "Nowadays people have to pass various tests for professional _____ so that they can be qualified for a well-paying job.",
      options: ["mechanics","permission","certificates","perseverance"],
      correct_option: "certificates"
  },
  {
      question: "Though Dr. Wang has been away from his hometown for over ten years, he can still _____ his old house clearly.",
      options: ["nominate","visualize","prolong","sprinkle"],
      correct_option: "visualize"
  },
  {
      question: "The speaker spent twenty minutes on one simple question. The explanation was so _____ that we could not see the point clearly.",
      options: ["coherent","crucial","various","lengthy"],
      correct_option: "lengthy"
  },
  {
      question: "The new tax policy proposed for the next fiscal year has been severely criticized by the ______ party leaders.",
      options: ["interaction","exposition","opposition","occupation"],
      correct_option: "opposition"
  },
  {
      question: "Thousands of people flooded into the city to join the demonstration; as a result, the city’s transportation system was almost ______.",
      options: ["testified","paralyzed","stabilized","dissatisfied"],
      correct_option: "paralyzed"
  },
]